[Applause]
Yes, so today, the three leaders of each group are all on the Niyajui-chan stage.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you for waiting, everyone.
This is the first time for all three leaders to get together.
First time.
It's the first time.
Yes, it is.
Oh, man, I'm nervous.
I'm nervous.
How are you doing?
Are you going to be a leader today?
I'll do my best.
I will do my best.
I know you may be a little tired, but I hope you will enjoy yourselves with me,
There's one thing that's been bothering me,
Moeiko calls me An-chan.
I see.
But when Moeko gets wise, she starts calling me Ana-san,
Ano-san.
That's right.
Which one of you is coming today?
An-chan?
Please.
Yay!
An-chan.
I don't like An-chan because she's too far away from me,
Please call me An-chan someday.
Someday.
Someday I can.
What do you call Moeko?
I had a warm meal the other day,
I told her so much that she should call me Moe-chan.
Neither of them called me Moe-chan,
So today is the day I'm going to ask him to call me Moe-chan.
I'll do my best if I can say it casually somewhere.
Please do.
Now, let me announce a project for the three leaders.
Let's call it,
The High Quality Supplies Contest!
This colorful leader's challenge!
Thank you very much.
So, each group of leaders will now challenge three different projects for a chance to win a premium gift box.
The group with the most points will be chosen.
The group with the most points will receive a sheet pack that will make them look even more beautiful.
Oh! I'm so happy!
What fun!
Let's move on to the first challenge.
This one is...,
Kendama Challenge!
All you have to do is stand on the stand over there and place the ball on the plate of the large bowl of kendama in one shot.
What do you want to do for 10 minutes?
What do you want to do?
But..,
What do I do?
To the bird, to the bird,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's not hot.
You were really good, Yasuda-san.
Hey, Ai-chan.
Aren't you fast? I can see it now.
Ai-chan.
You were really good.
I'm glad. Then, let me go last.
Ready!
Wow!
Cool!
Let's go!
So, what about you two?
Well, what do you think?
This is from the big cup.
That's right.
That'll be another 20.
Cool!
Please.
Yes, let's go in this order here.
Yes, please.
Please.
Okay.
Okay, Ai-chan, are you ready?
I'm ready.
Well, I guess I have to start putting pressure on myself.
How's it going?
You guys have to support me.
You can do anything, Ai-chan,
She's so dexterous.
I think she'll attack.
Oh, well.
But for Miyajima's sake,
Oh!
I'd like to celebrate the second anniversary in a big way.
Go for it!
I would like to go to Ai-chan's challenge.
Kendama Challenge, Ai-chan's challenge.
Thank you for your hard work.
We passed somehow, so we are
Team competition
It was a little bit dangerous, but
but we persevered.
I was nervous.
That's right.
More pressure was put on Moeiko, wasn't it?
The pressure came back to me.
Good luck.
How many of you have not played kendama?
Do you play kendama? Gentlemen...
I'll do it.
You do?
Oh, my God.
You're a big girl, aren't you?
You all think she can do it, don't you?
If it's Moeiko...
Moeiko is strong.
I'll go.
Let's leave it to Noimin-chan's leadership.
I'm ready.
Moeiko, please.
Wah!
Wow!
I'm coming!
Hey, guys.
It happens sometimes, doesn't it?
That was cool.
My thoughts were good, but...
I'm as nervous as a singing show
Hey, buddy.
I can't do it.
Just now...
I made a big show of it backstage.
I said so myself.
It's okay.
Stand up.
I'm taller than everyone.
Taller than anyone.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm going to do it! I'm going to do it! I'm going to do it!
Don't look at me. I'm shaking.
You're shaking.
Good luck!
Now for the Kendama challenge!
Here's An-chan's challenge!
Pop!
Oh, wow!
Three.
Two.
Oh!
Clap
Thanks for your hard work.
I'm looking forward to your kendo, Anta.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're really good.
It's okay if I'm a failure.
But I can do it, so watch me.
I'm going to stop writing about my skills for a minute.
Write, write, write.
Oh, my God.
You can do it.
That's Anna.
It's a success.
It's a success. Stop.
Don't worry about it. It's a failure.
It's a great success.
This is Ai, isn't it?
Congratulations.
Yay!
I want to practice kendama with you, too.
Good job, kendama!
Let's work hard as a leader team.
I'd like to continue.
Now let's go to the next challenge!
Here it is!
The third challenge is the HAKUUCHI WORD CHALLENGE!
Oh!
We're going to challenge you to say a word or two
You will each take a turn to speak a word.
However
If the first person succeeds
the next person will perform twice.
If the first one succeeds, the next one will do it three times, and so on.
and so on.
Yes, sir.
The first person to drop out gets zero points.
The two remaining players face off and the winner gets
2 points and the loser gets 1 point.
1 point to the loser.
I'll announce the subject.
Abrikarubee.
That's it.
We'll take turns on this one too.
One by one.
What shall we do?
I decided by janken (rock-paper-scissors-scissors), so...
Whoever wins...
First one is "goo" rock-paper-scissors.
Oh!
First one gets a "goo" rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll go.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, then.
I had to put pressure on him.
I can definitely fail as MC.
Let's not do it, let's not do it, let's not do it, let's not do it.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Let's get to it.
Let's try the rapid-fire word challenge!
End of the rapid-fire word challenge!
The rapid speech challenge is over!
Abhinikarbee!
Abrikarbi Abrikarbi Abrikarbi Abrikarbi Abrikarbi Abrikarbi Abrikarbi Abrikarbi
Abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi abrikarbi
So close!
That was so close!
I didn't cook the oiran!
I knew it! It's over!
I'm so sorry~
It was raw, wasn't it?
It was raw. I'm so disappointed!
We got married, and we continued...
Why don't you do this?
It's true, these two are important.
Yes, they are.
I'm sorry I've been so focused on this. I'm sorry.
How many times have you done this?
Yes, so Ai-chan is the word to drop out,
I will do my best.
Then I would like to participate in the finals.
I'm going to change my rapid-fire words.
Yes, what is it?
What kind of god anime, god anime, god anime.
Can you say it? Here we go.
Let's go.
A divine anime.
I don't want anyone to cheat.
You said "Crab anime", didn't you?
You're a crab, right?
You're a crab.
Crab?
Now for the finals.
Final round quick word challenge.
No, it's not.
Kami anime.
Gods of anime. Gods of anime.
This?
Divine anime. Divine anime. Divine anime.
It's hard.
Impossible!
This is impossible!
Paper animation
And I can definitely read this app.
It doesn't roll at all!
Definitely an app anime
The winner is
Points earned
Winner
Amazing
2 points earned
One point.
I got a point.
An-chan!
Kuraba-san gets 1 point
Akki
Collective point 0 this time
Raste has 1 point
It's a good match
Good match.
And, Minomi has 1 point.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
And now...
The last game of the night, ladies and gentlemen.
This way, please.
The Russian Marute!
Suddenly, the rollers are coming out.
Thank you very much.
They've collected my sword ball.
Swordballs.
There's only one pen that chirps.
The person who draws that one pen...
Oh, 2 points!
What?
That means you get 2 points for drawing the chiribiri pen!
Oh!
Variety, variety, variety!
Variety.
By the way, are you good at chiribiri?
I'm good at it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Shall I call Hitomi Takamatsu?
Oh, Nekone-san!
I knew it! She's our top reactionary.
This is for our points.
We have to choose a pen that's going to chatter on its own.
I see, we have to go chiri-chiri-chiri-chiri-chiri
We have to go and do the chattering.
And if it chirps, we'll be happy.
That's what we're going to do.
Then I'd like you to choose one.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
This one.
Oh, uh...
Okay, can I...?
I'll take care of it.
This way.
Yes, sir.
I can already feel it.
Not quite there yet.
That's a lie.
That's a lie
I guess this is our last challenge.
I hope you're all watching.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Cheer and support, everyone.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
And now, I challenge you to a little bit of Russian baillette.
You can wait. Ready?
Okay.
So, Blue is going crazy.
Yes!
How did you do?
Phrase! Phrase!
Ouch!
It hurts!
Good.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm already beautifully chattering.
So...
Coronavirus, you got 2 points for Anchan's team!
Congratulations!
So, we are going to aim for 3 points
Club-san Poiker, you are aiming for 3 points.
You have won a high class gift!
Thank you very much!
By the way, this one means you got a seal and a weapon, right?
Yes, I think so. After all, my age and skin is about to wear off,
What have I told you?
I'm afraid I'll fade and lose it,
I'm afraid.
I'm not afraid.
So, I'm going to pack a little luxury pack and make everyone prettier,
I want to enjoy the tour as much as I can!
Yes, I'm sure we will. And, you know, we lost this time,
How did you do? Ai-chan.
I was able to participate in the leaders' meeting,
I am so happy!
Yay!
Thank you so much.
Cute.
It was fun.
Thank you.
I also had a great time with Miya Jun-chan, the iconic collabo button, and Minmin,
I was happy to be able to spend time with everyone at the event like this,
I was happy that we were able to have an open recording together.
Thank you very much.
Now it is time for the ending.
How was everyone's viewing experience?
Thank you very much.
I had a great time with everyone.
That's all for now,
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
I won first place in the Elliman Challenge.
Thank you for your hard work.
You did your best.
Yes, I did. I did my best.
Let's all do our best.
Could you not ask me this one question?
You practiced really hard, didn't you?
Yes, we did. It went well, didn't it?
You did it so gently and well, didn't you?
I got it right the first time.
That's right.
But you won first place.
I see. What did you do?
I was the last one to get the last place.
I was so surprised.
Then, I won first place.
I got the first place,
That's great.
You won 100 yen?
That's great. I'm so happy.
Yes, I am. That's what I meant,
What is it?
A gift for you.
Yeah!
What?
Look.
It's a pack.
Are you sure?
Pack.
That's amazing.
I bought a lot.
Really?
I bought a lot of stuff.
It's a mess. This one.
What? It's good?
Yeah, it's good.
Yay. Thank you very much.
I'm so glad because I use the magic pack every day.
Do you think this will work for everyone on the tour?
For sure.
Let's do our best.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.